Antonio Vásquez Briones

+56992935020 – advasquezbr@gmail.com Concepción – Chile

Professional Profile

Automation Engineer with +3 years of experience working mainly in education of topics like Control Systems, Industrial Electronics, and Microcontrollers. Primarily focused on development and integration of new technologies. Excellent interpersonal and communication abilities, and possess a wide range of technical and programming skills. Enjoys being a part of a team, as well as managing, motivating and training others, and thrives in challenging working environments.

Education

- Universidad del Bío-Bío, Concepción Chile.
 - -Automation Engineer, 2014. (6 year degree)
 - -Bachelor of Science Degree in Engineering, 2013.
- Liceo Industrial Metodista, Coronel Chile.
 - -Electronics Technician, 2007.

Professional Experience

March 2015 to date	Universidad Tecnológica de Chile INACAP Concepción-Talcahuano.
	(Technological University of Chile)

- Full-time Academic of the Electrical, Electronics and Automation department, teaches mainly Control Systems, Microcontrollers and Industrial Networks classes. Teaches and trains adult and youth.
- SENCE Corporate Training Programs like Industrial Instruments and PLC
- Design and Implementation of Domotic Technologies at facilities.

August 2013 - March 2015. Liceo Industrial Metodista, Coronel

- Full-Time teacher for High-School Electronics Technicians, works with teenagers at social risk.
- Lead Teacher of the Robotics Group. First Prize at *Inacap Robotics Challenge 2014*.

August 2011 – August 2012 Industrial Instruments Field Technician

 Commissioning and troubleshooting at several power plants in Bío-Bío Region, Chile. Serves as English translator for companies from various locations around the world.

Marzo 2009 – Diciembre 2012 Universidad del Bío-Bío, Campus Concepción.

Teaching Assistant at Calculus, Motion Control and Systems courses.

Additional Skills

C/C++, Object Oriented Programming, Java, Processing, Arduino, Raspberry Pi, Python, Linux Systems, Assembly, Siemens Step 7, ABB IRC5 Robot System.